Thanh Pham

thanhpham091790@gmail.com | (720) 397-2824 7179 S Lincoln Way, Centennial, CO 80122

Human Resource Department

Dear Hiring Manager,

Please consider this letter as an expression of interest for the opening position that you have posted on your website. My name is Thanh Pham. I graduated with a Master's degree in Computer Science from Colorado Technical University. I have three years of practical experience in website development. With my education and collective work experiences, I look forward to the possibility of working on your team.

As mentioned above, I had spent three years as a web developer with Netbase JSC, in PHP developer, and technical team leader roles. They are one of the top outsourcing companies in Vietnam who focus on a total e-commerce solutions and consulting for all e-commerce businesses to sell products and services on the internet. During my time with the company, I was trained and obtained a lot experiences from their tasks and projects. The products that I have developed for the company are still available on their market place. Please refer the following link for my experiences at Netbase JSC:

o www.cmsmart.net/magento-extensions

Besides working with professional companies, I also work as a freelancer. I build websites that provide information about local business's products and services in Colorado. Although these are small and simple projects, it gives me the opportunity to practice many different aspects and new technologies of web development such as UI design, Bootstrap 4, React framework, and so on. Please refer some of my recently projects as a freelancer:

- o www.thanhhpham.com
- o www.upscalenaildenver.com

Typical skills I have gained throughout my experiences include:

- o HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- o Bootstrap 4, Flex-box, CSS-Grid
- o JQuery, Ajax, JSON
- o React framework
- o PHP, Node JS, Python

- o SQL, NoSQL (MySQL,
 - MongoDB)
- Version Control (Git, Github)
- o E-commerce website (Magento)
- o Agile/Scrum model

Please review the enclosed resume for additional information about my education and work experiences. You can also visit my portfolio at my own website to see examples of my work (www.phamhongthanh.com).

I look forward to talking with you about how my skills and experiences can benefit your opening position in more detail. Moreover, I can be reached anytime via my cell phone at (720) 397-2824 or via email at thanhpham091790@gmail.com.

Thank you for your time and consideration.

Sincerely, Thanh Pham

Thanh Pham

thanhpham091790@gmail.com | (720) 397-2824 7179 S Lincoln Way, Centennial, CO 80122

OBJECTIVE

I'm a very motivated, hardworking individual seeking long term employment in an organization where I can practice my knowledge, and skills as well as further enhance my experience in computer science field.

EDUCATION

Colorado Technical University

MS June 2020

Major: Computer Science

SKILLS

Web Development - 3+ years of experience in a professional work environment with a strong background in:

- o HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- o Bootstrap 4
- o React JS, JQuery
- o PHP, Node JS, Python
- o SQL, NoSQL
- o Version Control (Git), Agile/Scrum software development.
- o Experience building and maintaining E-commerce website (Magento).

Other:

- Excellent interpersonal skills including strong verbal, listening, and written communication.
- Technical leader skills including defining reality, answering technical questions, reviewing the member's decisions, and translating technical term for nontechnical stakeholders.

Bilingual:

o English & Vietnamese

EXPERIENCES

Freelancer – Outsourcing Developer

April 2018 - Now

- Developed and installed websites for local business in Colorado. Please refer my recently works at:
 - o http://www.thanhhpham.com.
 - o http://www.upscalenaildenver.com
- o Familiar with trending technologies such as Bootstrap 4, React JS, Python.

Netbase JSC – PHP Developer

Oct 2014 - Mar 2015

- Built featured products for company's market place. See all of my products at: https://cmsmart.net/magento-extensions
- Responded as a technical leader of extension team (team support, decision review, non-technical stakeholders)
- o Familiar with Agile/Scrum software development, decision maker.

Netbase JSC – PHP Developer Internship

Sep 2013 - Sep 2014

- o Experienced with PHP language, and e-commerce website (Magento).
- Familiar with the LAMP stack, MVC framework, OOP principles, and Git version control tool.

REFERENCES

Mr. Huy Nguyen

- Founder & CEO at Netbase JSC
- o LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/huynguyen9999
- Website: https://netbasejsc.com/